Guide to the Partners for Livable Communities collection, 1962-1994
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 13: Urban Planning, 1956-1994; (11 boxes)
  The largest section of the PLC collection after Series 3 (Central Business Districts), this series contains planning reports, policy statements, and congressional hearings on a wide range of urban planning and community development issues including economic development, land use, municipal tax policy, and suburban sprawl. Most of the materials deal with U.S. cities including Washington, D.C., Baltimore, Philadelphia, Madison, and Cincinatti, and such North American regions as Arizona, California, Texas, Oregon, New Jersey, Hawaii, Ontario, and British Columbia. However, it also contains studies on urban planning in China and a number of European countries including France, Italy, Spain, Poland, and the Netherlands. Within this series one will find numerous publications from the U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development, several studies on Court House Plaza in Arlington, a 1972 report on Fairfax County, The President's National Urban Policy Report of 1980 and 1988, Reports of the European Campaign for Urban Renaissance, meeting minutes of the Council of Europe's 5th Symposium in 1977, and a dozen case studies from the "States and Urban Strategies" series.
  - Affordable community: growth, change, and choice in the '80s, 1981 (Box 42, Volume 1)
    Council on Development Choices for the '80s
  - Alewife revitalization: Alewife urban design study phase II, 1979 (Box 42, Volume 2)
    Cambridge, MA Community Development Department
  - Alternative strategy for tackling the problems of outer housing estates, 1984 (Box 42, Volume 3)
    Jim R. Lloyd
  - America in the 1980s (Box 42, Volume 4)
    Hoyt Gimlin
  - American skyline, 1956 (Box 42, Volume 5)
    Christopher Tunnard,
  - American urban waterfront: a changing frontier, 1984 (Box 42, Volume 6)
    Leo Molinaro
  - Analyzing the economic feasibility of a development project: a guide for planners, 1983 (Box 42, Volume 7)
    Richard J. Roddewig
  - Anatomy of a competition: urban design for Milwaukee's lakefront, 1982 (Box 42, Volume 8)
    Lawrence P. Witzling
  - Area planning and resource management trends in northeastern Illinois, 1978-1979 (Box 42, Volume 9)
    Robert B. Teska
  - Arizona: precursor of post-industrial America, 1980 (Box 42, Volume 10)
    Paul Bracken
  - Background report of the downtown land use and transportation project, 1981 (Box 42, Volume 11)
    Seattle, Wash. Office of Policy and Evaluation
  - Ballungsgebiete in der Krise = Urban systems in crisis: understanding and planning human spaces: the biocybernetic approach, 1976 (Box 42, Volume 12)
    Frederic Vester
  - California Land Planning for People, 1975 (Box 42, Volume 13)
    Planning and Conservation Foundation
  - California State Land Use Planning, 1975 (Box 42, Volume 14)
  - Capital area greenway program: private land goes public, 1982 (Box 42, Volume 15)
    Arthur Jackson
  - Cincinnati Hillsides: the evolution of environmental quality zoning, 1980 (Box 42, Volume 16)
    Institute of Governmental Research
  - Cities of the United States: a compilation of current information on economic ... conditions. Vol. 1, The South, 1988 (Box 42, Volume 17)
    Deborah A. Straub
  - Cities of the United States: a compilation of current information on economic ... conditions. Vol. 2, The West, 1989 (Box 43, Volume 1)
    Peggy Saari
  - Cities of the United States: a compilation of current information on economic ... conditions. Vol. 3, The Midwest, 1990 (Box 43, Volume 2)
  - Cities of the United States: a compilation of current information on economic ... conditions. Vol. 4, The Northeast, 1990 (Box 43, Volume 3)
    Mary Reilly McCall
  - Citizen involvement: growing force in shaping urban decisions, 1980 (Box 43, Volume 4)
  - City need and the responsiveness of federal grants programs, 1978 (Box 43, Volume 5)
    Subcommittee on the City, 95th Congress, second session
  - City-suburb income gap: is it being narrowed by a back-to-the-city movement?, 1980 (Box 43, Volume 6)
    Larry H. Long and Donald C. Dahmann
  - Combatting cultural and commercial improvishment: the protection of financially vulnerable activities in urban renewal operations, 1981 (Box 43, Volume 7)
    Nicholas Falk
  - Community advisory visit report on Los Angeles county., 1980 (Box 43, Volume 8)
  - Conditions and quality of life in towns and cities: the concept of social balance, 1981 (Box 43, Volume 9)
    Markku Lankinen
  - Consoidated annual report to congress on community development programs, 1982 (Box 44, Volume 1)
  - Consoidated annual report to congress on community development programs, 1983 (Box 44, Volume 2)
  - Costs of sprawl: detailed cost analysis, 1974 (Box 44, Volume 3)
  - Costs of sprawl: executive summary, 1974 (Box 44, Volume 4)
  - Council on development choices for the '80s, undated (Box 44, Volume 5)
    Kenneth T. Jackson
  - Court House Plaza, undated (Box 44, Volume 6)
  - Court House Plaza, a place for all arlingtonians, 1981 (Box 44, Volume 7)
  - Court House Plaza sector plan, 1981 (Box 44, Volume 8)
  - Crown Point revitalization study, 1987 (Box 44, Volume 9)
  - Decentralization and urban policies: the French experience, 1984 (Box 44, Volume 10)
    Yves Dauge
  - Design Arts Program final report, grant to individual, 1984 (Box 44, Volume 11)
  - Design of the times, 1983 (Box 44, Volume 12)
    Kathy La Tour
  - Development choices for the 80s, interim report, 1980 (Box 44, Volume 13)
  - Development for whom? a critique of federal development policy, undated (Box 44, Volume 14)
    Roger J. Vaughan and June A. Sekera
  - Development framework guides regional land use, public facilities..., 1977 (Box 44, Volume 15)
    Twin Cities Metropolitan Council
  - Development of the nation's capital: hearings before the Committee on the District of Columbia House, 1977 (Box 44, Volume 16)
    House of Representatives, Ninety-Fifth Congress, first session
  - Development review and outlook 1983-1984 (Box 45, Volume 1)
  - Development review and outlook 1984-1985 (Box 45, Volume 2)
  - Economic Adjustment Program: Lower Peninsula of Virginia, 1979 (Box 45, Volume 3)
    Economic Adjustment Committee
  - Economic development prospects in British Columbia, 1979 (Box 45, Volume 4)
    Department of Regional Economic Expansion
  - Economic development prospects in Ontario, 1979 (Box 45, Volume 5)
  - Ekistics: the problems and science of human settlements, 1976 (Box 45, Volume 6)
    Gwen Bell, editor
  - Emerging trends in real estate: 1983 (Box 45, Volume 7)
  - Emerging trends in real estate: 1985 (Box 45, Volume 8)
  - Europe and the United States: new design in the city of fabric - negotiating for quality, 1984 (Box 45, Volume 9)
    Roy Worskett
  - European campaign for urban renaissance: increasing the influence of individuals... social balance 1, 1981 (Box 45, Volume 10)
  - European campaign for urban renaissance: increasing the influence of individuals... social balance 2, 1981 (Box 45, Volume 11)
  - European campaign for urban renaissance: towards a better social balance in towns and cities..., 1981 (Box 45, Volume 12)
  - European campaign for urban renaissance: report on the activities of Finland, 1982 (Box 45, Volume 13)
  - Evaluation of land use and development strategies for the Chattanooga/Hamilton County Regional Planning Commission, 1982 (Box 46, Volume 1)
  - Fairfax County, 1972 (Box 46, Volume 2)
    American Institute of Architects
  - Federal tax policy and urban development, 1977 (Box 46, Volume 3)
    House Committee on Banking, Finance and Urban Affairs, Ninety-Fifth Congress, first session
  - Fells Point urban design guide, 1976 (Box 46, Volume 4)
  - French new towns and innovation, 1973 (Box 46, Volume 5)
    J.E. Roullier
  - Future of urban housing in America, 1984 (Box 46, Volume 6)
    John J. Koelemij
  - Growth Shapers, 1976 (Box 46, Volume 7)
    Council on Environmental Quality
  - Hawaii's 'quiet revolution' hits the mainland, 1973 (Box 46, Volume 8)
    James Nathan Miller
  - Higher taxes that promote development, 1983 (Box 46, Volume 9)
    Gurney Breckenfeld
  - Housing policy in Catalonia: some experiences in rehabilitation of urban centres, 1984 (Box 46, Volume 10)
    Joan Rafols Esteve
  - IFHP News Sheet: Special issue - Belgium, 1981 (Box 46, Volume 11)
    International Federation for Housing and Planning
  - Impact evaluation of the urban development action grant program, 1982 (Box 46, Volume 12)
  - Impact of the aesthetic appearance of the urban environment: How important? How measured?, 1975 (Box 46, Volume 13)
    Philip S. Schaenman
  - Impact of the UDAG projects on the urban environment: survey and case studies, 1980 (Box 46, Volume 14)
    Kathryn Welch
  - Impediments to the economic, functional, and aesthetic development of the District of Columbia, 1977 (Box 46, Volume 15)
    House Committee on the District of Columbia, Ninety-Fifth Congress, first session
  - Improving Urban America: a challenge to federalism, 1976 (Box 46, Volume 16)
    Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations
  - Industrial development handbook, 1975 (Box 47, Volume 1)
  - Information Service, No. 25, March 1983 (Box 47, Volume 2)
  - Insurance redlining: a guide for action, undated (Box 47, Volume 3)
  - Kansas City urban design guidebook, 1978 (Box 47, Volume 4)
    City Development Department
  - Land policy in Sweden, 1976 (Box 47, Volume 5)
    Peter Heimburger
  - Land Use, 1974 (Box 47, Volume 6)
  - Land Use and Urban Development Impacts of Beltways, 1980 (Box 47, Volume 7)
    Payne-Maxie Consultants
  - Land use planning concepts, undated (Box 47, Volume 8)
  - Local economic development tools and techniques: a guidebook for local government, 1994 (Box 47, Volume 9)
  - Lower Swansea Valley: Legacy and Future, 1982 (Box 47, Volume 10)
    Swansea City Council Planning Department
  - Madison, Wisconsin: an evaluation of land use and development strategies for the University of Wisconsin-Madison, 1981 (Box 47, Volume 11)
  - Major development opportunities and issues in Canada's regions, 1979 (Box 47, Volume 12)
    Regional Economic Expansion
  - Making cities livable: lessons for the United States from Europe, 1980 (Box 47, Volume 13)
    Jonathan Barnett, Joseph Riley, etc.
  - Man and his urban environment: a manual of specific considerations for the seventies and beyond, undated (Box 47, Volume 14)
  - Managed growth: Has its time come?, 1973 (Box 47, Volume 15)
  - Managing Oregon's Growth: the politics of development planning, 1983 (Box 47, Volume 16)
    H. Jeffrey Leonard
  - Map-making as a part of current planning education in Japan, 1989 (Box 47, Volume 17)
    Yukio Nishimura
  - Matter of vision: community and economic development in the Philadelphia area, 1987 (Box 47, Volume 18)
    Haskell G. Ward,
  - Metropolitan regional governance: hearing before the Subcommittee on Intergovernmental Relations, 1984 (Box 47, Volume 19)
    Senate Committee on Governmental Affairs, Ninety-Eighth Congress, second session
  - Minneapolis Metro Center '85: a design solution, 1974 (Box 47, Volume 20)
    Weiming Lu
  - National Municipal Policy, 1984: adopted at the annual Congress of Cities, New Orleans, Louisiana, November 30, 1983 (Box 48, Volume 1)
  - National municipal policy, 1987: adopted at the annual business session, Congress of Cities, San Antonio, Texas, December 3, 1986 (Box 48, Volume 2)
    Congress of Cities
  - National policies for urban renewal, 1984 (Box 48, Volume 3)
    Lord Bellwin
  - Needs and demands for housing in urban areas, 1984 (Box 48, Volume 4)
    Hugo Priemus
  - Negotiated land development, 1983 (Box 48, Volume 5)
    Thompson R. Smith, D. Ernest Cook, and Peter R. Stein
  - Neighborhoods: Baltimore City, 1984-1987 (Box 48, Volume 6)
    Neighborhood Progress Administration
  - New buildings in old settings, 1982 (Box 48, Volume 7)
  - New towns planning and development: a world-wide bibliography, 1973 (Box 48, Volume 8)
  - Oblique aerial photography for comprehensive urban planning, 1981 (Box 48, Volume 9)
    Frank E. Reynolds`
  - Palo Alto/Stanford Forum, 1978-1980: the evolution of a decision forming process (Box 48, Volume 10)
  - Pelican Bay: an evaluation of the land use and development strategies, 1977 (Box 48, Volume 11)
  - Phoenix: Rx for planned development, 1974 (Box 48, Volume 12)
    American Institute for Architects
  - Plan for Urban Growth: Report of the National Policy Task Force, 1972 (Box 48, Volume 13)
  - Planners' Salaries and Employment Trends, 1983, 1984 (Box 48, Volume 14)
    James Hecimovich and JoAnn C. Butler
  - Planning and development in the Netherlands, 1976 (Box 48, Volume 15)
  - Planning for enterprise, 1982 (Box 48, Volume 16)
  - Planning New Towns: National Reports of the U.S. and the U.S.S.R., 1981 (Box 48, Volume 17)
  - Political Choice and Public Allocation in City Planning (Box 48, Volume 18)
    Joop Linthorst
  - President's national urban policy report, 1980. Executive summary (Box 48, Volume 19)
  - President's national urban policy report, 1988 (Box 48, Volume 20)
  - Problems of Deteriorated Areas: Policies of Conservation and Rehabilitation in Spain, 1984 (Box 49, Volume 1)
    Francisco Pol
  - Proceedings: Builders examine the many faces of homelessness, 1988 (Box 49, Volume 2)
    Home Builders Institute and the National Association of Home Builders
  - Progress guide and general plan, 1978 (Box 49, Volume 3)
    San Diego Planning Commission
  - Psychological Aspects of Urbanology, 1966 (Box 49, Volume 4)
  - Public facilities manual. Vol. I: 1982 update adopted by the Fairfax County Board of Supervisors on February 7, 1983 ... (Box 49, Volume 5)
  - Rebuilding America's Cities: Roads to Recovery, 1984 (Box 49, Volume 6)
    Paul R. Porter and David C. Sweet
  - Regeneration of Mersyside Docklands, 1984 (Box 49, Volume 7)
    Basil Bean
  - Remarks for Michael Pittas, Minneapolis College of Art and Design Lecture Series, Cities: an Urban Overview, 1982 (Box 49, Volume 8)
  - Reshaping Winter Cities: Concepts, Strategies and Trends, 1985 (Box 49, Volume 9)
    Norman E.P. Pressman
  - Resource Allocation and Comprehensive Planning: Summary of a California Tomorrow Seminar on the Use of Land Resources, 1975 (Box 49, Volume 10)
    Anthony F. Gantner, editor, California Tomorrow
  - Revitalizing downtown: a national videoconference, 1984 (Box 49, Volume 11)
  - Rincon Hill, 1981 (Box 49, Volume 12)
    San Francisco Department of City Planning
  - River City, 1985 (Box 49, Volume 13)
    New Jersey Committee, Regional Plan Association
  - Role of the French New Towns in Regional Development and Regional Life, 1972 (Box 49, Volume 14)
    J.P. Lacaze
  - Show and Tell Presentations: brief reports on urban development in the Europe and the Middle East (Box 49, Volume 15)
  - Site planning evaluation methodology, 1974 (Box 49, Volume 16)
  - Sixth Annual Community Development Block Grant Report, 1981 (Box 49, Volume 17)
  - Slowing of urbanization in the U.S., 1983 (Box 50, Volume 1)
    Larry H. Long
  - Small cities and counties: a guide to managing services, 1984 (Box 50, Volume 2)
    James M. Banovetz, International City Management Association
  - Small city redevelopment strategies in Ohio, volume 1, 1980 (Box 50, Volume 3)
  - Socially responsible community planning: applied social impact, 1979 (Box 50, Volume 4)
    Ministry of Municipal Affairs
  - State urban development strategies, 1977 (Box 50, Volume 5)
    Dwight E. Jensen, editor
  - Staten Island: Planning for the Future, 1977 (Box 50, Volume 6)
    City of New York Department of Planning
  - States and Urban Strategies: California's Urban Strategy, 1980 (Box 50, Volume 7)
    Lizette Weiss
  - States and Urban Strategies: A Communities Strategy in Florida, 1980 (Box 50, Volume 8)
    Richard G. RuBino
  - States and Urban Strategies: A Comparative Analysis, 1980 (Box 50, Volume 9)
    Charles R. Warren
  - States and Urban Strategies: Connecticut's Urban Strategy, 1980 (Box 50, Volume 10)
    Morton J. Tenzer and Carol Lewis
  - States and Urban Strategies: Executive Summary, 1980 (Box 50, Volume 11)
  - States and Urban Strategies: Massachusetts' Urban Strategy: The Dukakis Years, 1980 (Box 50, Volume 12)
    William M. Capron
  - States and Urban Strategies: Michigan's State Urban Strategies, 1980 (Box 50, Volume 13)
    David Cason, Jr.
  - States and Urban Strategies: New Jersey's Urban Strategy, 1980 (Box 50, Volume 14)
    Richard Lehne and James Robinson
  - States and Urban Strategies: North Carolina's Balanced Growth Stragety, 1980 (Box 50, Volume 15)
    Deil S. Wright
  - States and Urban Strategies: A Non-Intervention Approach, 1980 (Box 50, Volume 16)
    James G. Coke
  - States and Urban Strategies: Oregon's State Urban Strategy, 1980 (Box 50, Volume 17)
    John M. DeGrove and Nancy E. Stroud
  - States and Urban Strategies: State Urban Policy in Pennsylvania, 1980 (Box 50, Volume 18)
    Charles M. Christian and Connie L. Williams
  - State's Role in Urban Economic Development: An Urban Government Perspective, 1980 (Box 50, Volume 19)
    Leanne Aronson and Carol Shapiro
  - Strategies for Livable Places: Design for Smaller Communities, 1981 (Box 50, Volume 20)
    Minnesota Chapter of the American Planning Association
  - Street-Level Governments: Assessing Decentralization and Urban Services, 1975 (Box 50, Volume 21)
    Robert K. Yin and Douglas Yates
  - Structure for a national growth policy, 1973 (Box 51, Volume 1)
  - Study design: neighborhood planning in Atlanta, 1976-1977 (Box 51, Volume 2)
    Department of Budget and Planning, Atlanta, Georgia
  - Success abroad: what foreign cities can teach American cities, 1977 (Box 51, Volume 3)
  - Survey of citizen views and concerns about urban life, 1978 (Box 51, Volume 4)
  - Survival strategies: Paris and New York, 1979 (Box 51, Volume 5)
    George G. Wynne
  - Symposium No. 5, Granada: Co-report on general theme: Rural architecture in regional planning, October 26-29, 1977 (Box 51, Volume 6)
    Jacques Houlet, Council of Europe
  - Symposium No. 5, Granada: Report on general theme: Rural architecture in regional planning, October 26-29, 1977 (Box 51, Volume 7)
    Manuel Ribas i Piera, Council of Europe
  - Symposium No. 5, Granada: Co-report on theme 1: Rural architecture: its cultural values and development, October 26-29, 1977 (Box 51, Volume 8)
    Hans-Ole Hansen, Council of Europe
  - Symposium No. 5, Granada: Report on theme 1: Rural Architecture: its cultural values and development, October 26-29, 1977 (Box 51, Volume 9)
    Efren Garcia Fernandez, Council of Europe
  - Symposium No. 5, Granada: Co-eport on theme II: Integrated conservation of rural architecture and socio-economic development, October 26-29, 1977 (Box 51, Volume 10)
    Lucio Gambi, Council of Europe
  - Symposium No. 5, Granada: Report on theme II: Integrated conservation of rural architecture and socio-economic development, October 26-29, 1977 (Box 51, Volume 11)
    Jesus Leal and Roberto Sancho, Council of Europe
  - Symposium No. 5, Granada: Co-report on theme III: Rural architecture: a factor in regional planning policy, October 26-29, 1977 (Box 51, Volume 12)
    Jean-Pierre Vouga, Council of Europe
  - Symposium No. 5, Granada: Report on theme III: Rural architecture: a factor in regional planning policy, October 26-29, 1977 (Box 51, Volume 13)
    Fernando Fernandez-Cavada, Council of Europe
  - Third Sector in Urban Development, 1981 (Box 51, Volume 14)
    Jack Robertson and Andrew Euston
  - To save a city, 1977 (Box 51, Volume 15)
    Congressman Henry S. Reuss, House Committee on Banking, Finance and Urban Affairs, Ninety-Fifth Congress, first session
  - Towns and Cities, 1966 (Box 51, Volume 16)
    Emrys Jones
  - Towns and cities in social balance: a seminar report, 1981 (Box 51, Volume 17)
  - Township funding opportunities: a guide to federal resources for small communities, 1981 (Box 51, Volume 18)
    National Association of Towns and Townships
  - Up Greenhill and Down the Dale: an interpretive plan for Wirksworth, Derbyshire, 1983 (Box 51, Volume 19)
    Civic Trust/Center for Environmental Interpretation
  - Urban action: a new partnership to conserve America's communities: a report after one year, undated (Box 51, Volume 20)
    U.S. President's Interagency Coordinating Council
  - Urban America: Policies and Problems, 1978 (Box 51, Volume 21)
    Congressional Quarterly, Inc.
  - Urban and Regional Development Statistics: Republic of China, 1982 (Box 52, Volume 1)
    Council for Economic Planning and Development, Executive Yuan
  - Urban and Regional Development Statistics: Republic of China, 1983 (Box 52, Volume 2)
  - Urban conservation and federally assisted economic development in cities: putting it together, 1980 (Box 52, Volume 3)
    Phyllis Myers, The Conservation Foundation
  - Urban conservation and urban economic development: collision and convergence, 1980 (Box 52, Volume 4)
  - Urban design: concept process, goals and implementation - the Lubbock experience, Texas, 1982 (Box 52, Volume 5)
    James E. Bergram and James D. Mertes, APA
  - Urban impact of federal policies: a preview of a new Rand study, 1977 (Box 52, Volume 6)
    Mark J. Kasoff
  - Urban impacts of federal policies. Vol. 4, Population and residential location, 1979 (Box 52, Volume 7)
    Roger J. Vaughan
  - Urban planning in China, 1979 (Box 52, Volume 8)
    Edwin A. Winckler and Janet A. Cady
  - Urban policy and public opinion, 1979 (Box 52, Volume 9)
    Center for Urban Studies
  - Urban Problems and Policies: Common Problems - Different Solutions?, 1984 (Box 52, Volume 10)
    Peter Hall
  - Urban Renewal Participation Experiments: Heralds of a New Local Democracy?, 1982 (Box 52, Volume 11)
    N.J.M. Nelissen, Council of European Municipalities, Dutch Section
  - Urbanisme, September 1987, No. 221: Les Regions et L'Amenagement, 1989 (Box 52, Volume 12)
  - Using Microcomputers in Urban Planning, 1982 (Box 52, Volume 13)
    William L. Whited
  - Warszawa 1970-1985, 1971 (Box 52, Volume 14)
    Stanislaw Jankowski, Warsaw Town Planning Office
  - Why Study Venice?, 1972 (Box 52, Volume 15)
    Richard Bartholomew
  - Zero Lot Line Development, 1982 (Box 52, Volume 16)
- Series 14: Oversize, 1967-1987; (2 boxes)
  This series contains oversize books on subjects that would otherwise be included in the following series: Central Business Districts, Cultural Facilities, Open Spaces, Parks and Recreation, and Urban Planning. It contains studies and planning proposals with large color photographs on San Diego, San Francisco, Baton Rouge, Chicago, and Providence, as well as Dublin, Ireland, and the Hague.
  - Baton Rouge: the arts capitalized, 1984 (Box 53, Volume 1)
    Bryce Moreland
  - Chicago 21: a plan for the Central Area communities, 1973 (Box 53, Volume 2)
    Chicago Plan Commission
  - Discover Providence: The Providence City Spirit Project, 1976 (Box 53, Volume 3)
    Johnette L. Isham
  - Dublin: a city in crisis, 1975 (Box 53, Volume 4)
    Dublin Urban Study
  - Haagse Stadhuis centraal / Hague Town Hall Central, 1987 (Box 53, Volume 5)
  - Imagine Bayfront Park, 1985 (Box 53, Volume 6)
  - Interface Providence, 1974 (Box 53, Volume 7)
    Interface Providence Design Team
  - Public Participation in Regional Planning, 1967 (Box 54, Volume 1)
    Regional Plan Association
  - KMcLD: presentation of recent projects by Kaplan/McLaughlin/Diaz, undated (Box 54, Volume 2)
  - Rebuilding Central Park: A Management and Restoration Plan, 1979 (Box 54, Volume 3)
  - Request for qualifications, mixed-use development: Yerba Buena Center, downtown San Francisco, 1980 (Box 54, Volume 4)
  - St. Johns building improvement handbook, 1978 (Box 54, Volume 5)